Thank you so much for picking me up.
Yeah, no problem.
I just got to go pick up my books. I'll be right back.
- Don't go anywhere. - No problem, I'll be right here.
[ ENGLISH AS SECOND LANGUAGE ] Welcome !
- What is your name ? - Uh, I'm Joey.
Joey, you have a wonderful accent.
Thank you.
Joey, are you sure you're in the right place ?
Oh, I'm in the right place.
Let's get  started.
- One. - One.
Two... Three...
Four... Five...
Six... Seven...
Eight... Nine... Ten !
Eleven,  Twelve.
Very good, Boris.
thanks, thanks.
13, 14, 15.
[Music]
Oh, Joey. Your English so good.
Can you say  more words for me ?
Uh...
"Corduroy."
Give me another.
"Harpsichord."
Oh, yes.
Now this is  a big one.
Don't do it. It's too dangerous !
"Ibuprofen."
Get the check.
What happened to you ? I had to call Alex for a ride.
Oh, my God ! What a body !
I haven't felt this way since gymnastics camp.
Hey, Maria !
Take me to the car, you sexy bastard.
[Music]
Bill... and Mary go to
Ssss....
Schhhh....
"School", Renata ! They go to school.
Okay... Joey, why don't you pick it up where Renata left off ?
Now, this is a hard part.
So take your time.
Oh, boy, yeah. This is-- This looks tough.
"The bell rang and the students all went to  the auditorium with their teacher." Boom !
That's right, Boris. You heard it...
"Auditorium" !
I am so lucky to be with the smartest boy in class.
Some words are so tug.
"Tug" ?
Oh, remember, I told you the GH sometimes sounds like an F.
It's "tough". Like "rough" or "laugh".
Oh, Joey, make love to me tonigh-F-t.
That ...is good English.
Okay...
I'd like everybody to take out their homework on the subjunctive tense.
You didn't do it ??
I got it.
If the present tense of the verb to be is "I am"...
then the subjunctive tense is "if I..." ?
Joey.
"If I was."
That's not correct.
It's, uh... "if I were."
Very good, Boris.
[Laughter]
🎵Joey are stupid. 🎶
"Joey IS stupid", Renata !
[Applause]
[Music]
Ah, Maria... I totally forgot.
I can't go on a picnic today, I have to study.
But why ? It's just a stupid class.
"A stupid class" !?!
Maria, my studies are very important to me.
Yes, but there is a nice park to go to.
Okay... first of all, you don't end a sentence with the preposition.
Okay, that is wrong.
In fact, lately, everything about you is wrong.
Except for your awesome, awesome body !
And I'm afraid, I'm gonna have to say goodbye Maria.
- But what about us ? - You know, he said goodbye.
[SPANISH] Pues ¡ Quédate aquí con tu mujerzuela !
- What'd she say ? - She thinks I'm your whore.
Can anyone give me an example  of a multiple homonym ?
I can !
"They're" meaning "they are",
"their" meaning group possessive... and "there" meaning "in that place".
That's very good, Joey.
- Joey wins the prize. - YES !!
Thank you. I would like to share another American phrase with all of you.
Uh, "SUCK IT !"
Have fun studying, Joey.